Treeger:
OH, MAN!
WHAT IS THAT?
TREEGER'S SNAKING
THE SHOWER DRAIN.
OH.
Treeger:
WHAT IN THE NAME
OF HELL...?!
HEY, MAYBE HE FOUND
YOUR FLIP-FLOP.
HEY...
WHOA.
IS THIS PORN?
WHAT DID I DO?
I MUST'VE
HIT SOMETHING
ON THE REMOTE.
DO WE PAY FOR THIS?
NO, WE DIDN'T EVEN PAY
OUR CABLE BILL.
MAYBE THIS IS
HOW THEY PUNISH US.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T PAY
OUR PHONE BILL.
FREE PHONE SEX.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T PAY
OUR GAS BILL.
WHOA, HEY, THAT LADY'S
ALL KINDS OF NAKED.
YEAH, JOEY JUST PRESSED
SOMETHING ON THE REMOTE
AND IT JUST... CAME ON.
HEY, THAT HAPPENED
TO ME ONCE.
I WAS JUST FLIPPING
THROUGH THE CHANNELS, AND BAM!
IT WAS LIKE FINDING MONEY.
LIKE FINDING MONEY
WITH NAKED PEOPLE ON IT.
THEN I MADE THE MISTAKE
OF TURNING OFF THE TV.
I NEVER GOT IT BACK AGAIN.
AND I'M SAD.
WHY WOULD HE
TURN OFF THE TV?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
( slow, sensuous music playing)
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
COME ON, DO WE REALLY HAVE
TO WATCH THIS WHILE WE EAT?
NO! NO! NO!
NO! NO! NO! NO!
WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT COULD MAKE
THIS GO AWAY.
YEAH, SO NO ONE
TOUCHES THE REMOTE
AND NO ONE
TOUCHES THE TV.
AND NO ONE TOUCHES THE AIR...
AROUND THE TV.
IMAGINE A
PROTECTIVE PORN
BUBBLE, IF YOU WILL.
OKAY?
I'M AT LEAST
GOING TO MUTE IT.
NO-NO-NO!
( music stops )
WE STILL HAVE PORN.
YEAH.
HI.
HEY.
HONEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT'S TOO HEAVY.
COME HERE.
THANKS.
OH, GOD...
OKAY.
OH, HONEY...
I'M GETTING TOO PREGNANT
FOR THIS...
LUGGING AROUND A
STUPID MASSAGE TABLE.
I HAVE TO FIND A
JOB WHERE I CARRY
A SMALLER TABLE.
OR A JOB
WHERE YOU DON'T
HAVE TO CARRY
A TABLE.
YOU MEAN
LIKE A DOCTOR?
PHEEBS, YOU'RE
BLOCKING THE PORN.
LOOK OUT.
OHH.
OH, MY.
OH, THAT REMINDS ME--
I HAVE TO SEE MY OB-GYN TODAY.
HI.
SO, UH, EMILY JUST WENT
TO THE AIRPORT.
OH. WHY DIDN'T YOU TAKE HER?
HER UNCLE HAD ALREADY
PLANNED ON DOING IT
AND, YOU KNOW, WE
SAID OUR GOOD-BYES
THIS MORNING, SO...
YOU MUST FEEL HORRIBLE.
HEY, THE GUYS HAVE FREE PORN.
NO...
HEY, CHEER UP.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE
HER AGAIN, RIGHT?
WELL, I...
THAT'S THE THING.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN I BROUGHT IT UP,
SHE SAID "THIS IS SO FANTASTIC.
"WHY DO WE HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT THE FUTURE?
LET'S JUST ENJOY..."
NO, YOU... D-DON'T
DO THE ACCENT.
HEY, YOU'VE GOT
TO SEE HER AGAIN.
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH?
BECAUSE...
YOU COULD GET TO
LIVE OUT MY FANTASY.
YOU'VE HAD FANTASIES
ABOUT EMILY?
NO. YOU KNOW.
THE FANTASY.
MEET SOMEONE FROM
A STRANGE LAND,
FALL IN LOVE
AND SPEND THE REST OF
YOUR LIVES TOGETHER.
IS THAT WHY IN JUNIOR HIGH
YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
WHO HUNG OUT
WITH THAT UKRAINIAN KID?
YEAH, THAT, BUT...
PLUS HIS MOM USED TO PUT
SOUR CREAM ON EVERYTHING.
AH...
DO YOU LOVE HER?
WE SAID IT WAS ONLY GOING
TO BE TWO WEEKS, YOU KNOW?
YOU LOVE HER.
WHA-WHAT IS LOVE, REALLY?
OH...
I KNEW YOU LOVED HER.
YOU NEED TO GO TO THE
AIRPORT AND TELL HER.
YOU'LL PROBABLY CATCH HER
JUST AS SHE'S ABOUT
TO GO TO THE GATE.
YOU'RE GOING TO CALL
OUT HER NAME, AND YELL
"I LOVE YOU," AND
SHE'S GOING TO SAY
"I LOVE YOU, TOO"
AND THEN YOU GUYS
ARE GOING TO HAVE
THE MOST AMAZING KISS
AND EVERYONE AT THE GATE
WILL APPLAUD.
I AM A GOOD KISSER.
WELL, THEN YOU TWO CAN...
CAN SNEAK INTO
THE COCKPIT...
AND THINGS'LL START
TO HEAT UP...
( panting )
AND THEN A STEWARDESS
COMES IN...
I'VE BEEN WATCHING
TOO MUCH PORN.
( rhythmic whooshing )
( gasps )
IS THAT THE
HEARTBEAT?
THAT'S IT.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, WOW, THIS IS SO COOL.
HAVE WE TALKED ABOUT
THE POSSIBILITY
OF MULTIPLE BIRTHS?
WELL, WHY DON'T WE JUST
TAKE CARE OF THIS ONE
AND SHOULD I GET PREGNANT AGAIN,
I'LL HOLD ON TO YOUR CARD, OKAY?
NO.
I'M GETTING THREE
SEPARATE HEARTBEATS.
THREE? YOU GUYS WERE WORRIED
I WOULDN'T EVEN HAVE ONE.
DOCTORS ARE WRONG
ALL THE TIME.
WELL...
WELL, SO ARE YOU SURE
THAT THERE ARE THREE?
DEFINITELY.
OH, MY GOD.
SO... SO IN A FEW MONTHS
I'M GOING TO HAVE
THREE FULL-GROWN BABIES
JUST WALKING AROUND INSIDE ME?
OH, OH! AND IT'S GOING TO BE
LIKE ONE OF THOSE LOG RIDES
WHEN THEY JUST COME
SHOOTING OUT.
GIVING BIRTH
TO THREE BABIES
IS NOT THAT DIFFERENT
THAN GIVING BIRTH TO ONE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
OH, OH... PHOEBE.
OH! HI.
HI!
SO, HOW'D IT GO
AT THE DOCTOR'S?
OH, WELL, OKAY.
HEY, YOU KNOW
HOW WHEN YOU'RE
UM, YOU'RE WALKING
DOWN THE STREET
AND YOU SEE
THREE PEOPLE IN A ROW
AND YOU SAY,
"OH, THAT'S NICE"?
YES!
OKAY.
YEAH, WELL
GOOD NEWS-- YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE THREE BABIES. AH!
( laughing )
THREE BABIES?
UH-HUH.
( laughing )
OH... I FINALLY GOT MY BAND!
OH, OH...
( laughing )
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A BIG FAMILY.
I ALWAYS WANTED
A BIG FAMILY!
OH, GOD
I'M SO GLAD YOU GUYS
ARE HAPPY.
I WAS SO AFRAID YOU WERE
GOING TO BE ALL FREAKED.
WHY WOULD WE
BE FREAKED?
NO, 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE IT'S HARDER
TO RAISE THEM,
AND THE ADDED EXPENSE AND, UGH!
OH.
RIGHT.
NO. BACK TO HAPPY.
BACK TO HAPPY!
NO, NO, NO, NO...
IT'S GOING TO BE
FINE BECAUSE, UM...
BECAUSE I TEACH HOME EC
AND, UH, I CAN
HAVE 30 KIDS
MAKING BABY CLOTHES
ALL YEAR LONG.
YOU KNOW, IT'LL BE LIKE...
MY VERY OWN
LITTLE SWEAT SHOP.
I BEEN THINKING
EVER SINCE YOU SAID
THAT WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TRIPLETS...
THE BEST THING
FOR ME TO DO IS
DROP OUT OF COLLEGE
AND GET A JOB.
NO, FRANK.
NO, YOU CAN'T QUIT COLLEGE. NO.
YOU'RE IN COLLEGE, REALLY?
YEAH, REFRIGERATOR
COLLEGE.
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW
WHEN WE FOUND OUT
WE WERE GOING TO HAVE
A BABY, YOU KNOW
I FIGURED, YOU KNOW,
LIKE, I SHOULD HAVE...
LIKE A CAREER, YOU KNOW
AND I LOVE
REFRIGERATORS.
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP ON YOUR DREAM.
( groans )
NO, IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE THREE KIDS
AND THAT'S A DIFFERENT
KIND OF DREAM.
THREE KIDS AND NO MONEY.
( woman over P.A. system):
This is the boarding call
for flight 0-0-9.
Ross:
EMILY...
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST... I HAD TO
SEE YOU ONE MORE TIME
BEFORE YOU TOOK OFF.
YOU ARE SO SWEET.
THAT'S-THAT'S
A BIG CANDY BAR.
I HAD THE MOST AMAZING
TIME WITH YOU.
ME, TOO.
This is the final boarding call
for flight 0-0-9.
WELL, THAT'S ME.
HERE, HAVE THIS--
I'M ONLY ALLOWED
ONE PIECE OF CARRY-ON ANYWAY.
( laughs )
WAIT.
UH... LISTEN, I-I...
I HAVE TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING. UM...
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
I'M JUST GOING TO COME
OUT AND SAY IT, OKAY?
UH... I... I THINK...
I LOVE YOU.
OH.
THANK YOU.
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
♪ BOW CHICKA BOW-WOW. ♪
WHAT IS THAT SONG?
IT'S BEEN IN MY HEAD
ALL DAY.
IT'S THE THEME
FROM GOOD WILL HUMPING.
YOU KNOW WHO DOESN'T EVEN LIKE
DIRTY MOVIES?
MY NEW BOYFRIEND, JOSHUA.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, HE TOLD ME
HE PREFERS TO LEAVE
CERTAIN THINGS
TO THE IMAGINATION.
OH, OH, YEAH, AND
DID HE ALSO SAY
THAT HE THOUGHT THAT SOME
OF THE DIALOGUE WAS CORNY
AND THAT HE ACTUALLY
FOUND IT FUNNY, NOT SEXY?
YES!
YEAH, HE LIKES PORN.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M GOING TO FIND OUT
IF HE REALLY THINKS
SUPERMODELS ARE TOO SKINNY.
HEY.
HI.
HOW'D IT GO
WITH FRANK AND ALICE?
WELL, FRANK HAS TO QUIT COLLEGE
BECAUSE HIS
SUPERFERTILE SISTER'S
HAVING THREE BABIES. UGH.
SO I NEED TO MAKE
A LOT OF MONEY REALLY FAST
AND I HAD AN IDEA THAT
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
'CAUSE YOU WORK
FOR A BIG COMPANY.
OKAY. INSIDER TRADING.
WHAT INFORMATION
IS THERE
THAT YOU CAN GIVE ME?
THEY DON'T REALLY TALK TO US
ABOUT THAT STUFF.
I COULD GET YOU
SOME FREE WITE-OUT, THOUGH.
DID YOU DO WHAT I SAID?
DID YOU TELL HER?
I DID.
AND...? WHAT'D SHE SAY?
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE TOTALLY WELCOME.
WHAT'D SHE SAY?
SHE SAID, "THANK YOU."
I SAID, "I LOVE YOU"
AND SHE SAID...
"THANK YOU."
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
DID YOU SAY
YOU LOVE HER?
YEAH, WHAT WERE YOU TRYING
TO GET HER TO DO?
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
WELL, YOU PLAY HARD TO GET.
SHE ALREADY LIVES IN LONDON.
OH. SO YOU GO TO TOKYO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
FORGET IT.
OKAY? FORGET IT.
YOU TOLD HER YOU
LOVE HER. IT'S OVER.
IT IS NOT OVER.
YOU'RE OVER.
WHAT?
YOU KNOW.
OKAY.
GOOD ONE.
IT IS NOT OVER
BECAUSE SHE'S GOING TO CALL YOU
AND TELL YOU SHE LOVES YOU,
AND THE REASON SHE COULDN'T
IS HER FEELINGS
WERE SO STRONG IT SCARED HER.
GO HOME AND WAIT
FOR HER CALL.
SHE COULD BE CALLING
FROM THE PLANE.
COME ON, NOW. GO, GO.
OKAY, OKAY
BUT IF SHE DOESN'T CALL,
IT IS DEFINITELY OVER.
NO, WAIT, WAIT--
UNLESS, EVENTUALLY
I CALL HER, YOU KNOW,
TO-TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON
AND-AND SHE SAYS,
SHE'LL CALL ME BACK
BUT THEN SHE DOESN'T
THEN... IT'S OVER.
WAY TO BE STRONG, MAN.
HI.
HEY.
CAN WE WATCH CARTOONS
ON YOUR TELEVISION?
WE NEED A PORN BREAK.
WE SPENT THE LAST TWO HOURS
WATCHING IN AND OUT
AND IN AGAIN.
WELL, SO, WHY DON'T
YOU JUST TURN IT OFF?
BECAUSE THEN
WE'D BE THE GUYS
WHO TURNED OFF FREE PORN.
OH! GOOD. YOU'RE HERE.
HI.
HEY, HI.
WHAT YOU
GOT THERE?
OH, THIS?
WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU ASKED.
NOW, DON'T YOU HATE IT
WHEN YOU HAVE TO CUT A TIN CAN
WITH AN ORDINARY STEAK KNIFE?
HA.
NOW, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
PREGNANT WOMAN SLAYS FOUR?
Monica:
PHOEBE, THEY DIDN'T
MAKE YOU PAY FOR
THOSE KNIFES,
DID THEY?
NO.
ARE YOU SURE?
HONEY, YOU
WON'T MAKE
ENOUGH MONEY TO HELP
FRANK AND ALICE
JUST BY SELLING KNIVES.
NO, NO. I KNOW THAT.
I JUST NEED TO MAKE ENOUGH
FOR THE SECOND PART OF MY PLAN.
WHAT'S THE SECOND PART?
MY SATURN DEALERSHIP.
( phone ringing )
HELLO?
ROSS.
EMILY, HI.
UH...
HOW WAS, HOW WAS YOUR FLIGHT?
It was dreadful.
I FELT TERRIBLE
ABOUT HOW I ACTED
WHEN YOU SAID
THOSE WONDERFUL THINGS.
NO, NO.
TH-THAT'S-THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
UM... I'M JUST GLAD YOU CALLED.
Ross, um...
there's something
that I-I've got to tell you.
UH, THERE'S-THERE'S
SOMEONE ELSE.
DOES THAT MEAN
THE SAME THING IN ENGLAND
AS IT DOES IN AMERICA?
SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHICH ONE
OF US SHE WANTS--
ME OR THIS
COLIN GUY.
THIS ISN'T HOW
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO GO.
THERE CAN'T BE ANOTHER GUY.
WELL.
OF COURSE, THERE'S
ANOTHER GUY!
THIS IS EVEN MORE PERFECT.
NOW YOU HAVE TO PROVE YOUR LOVE.
I'M NOT PROVING ANYTHING.
OKAY? I'M DONE
LISTENING TO YOU.
IF I HADN'T LET
YOU TALK ME INTO GOING
TO THE AIRPORT
IN THE FIRST PLACE
I NEVER WOULD HAVE PUT
MY FIST THROUGH THE WALL.
YOU PUT YOUR FIST
THROUGH THE WALL?
NO, I MISSED AND HIT THE DOOR...
BUT IT OPENED REALLY HARD.
YOU HAVE TO GO
TO LONDON.
WHAT?
YEAH, YOU HAVE TO GO
FIGHT FOR HER.
OH, YEAH, THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU ALREADY TOLD HER
YOU LOVED HER
AND SHE DIDN'T SAY IT BACK.
THEN SHE CALLED AND TOLD YOU
THERE WAS ANOTHER GUY
SO, YEAH, GO TO LONDON;
THAT'LL SCARE HER.
WHEN RACHEL WAS WITH PAOLO,
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I MADE FUN OF HIS ACCENT.
YOU SAT BACK
AND LET HIM HAVE HER.
YOU DIDN'T FIGHT AT ALL;
AM I RIGHT?
WANT THE SAME THING
TO HAPPEN?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
GO FIGHT FOR HER.
GO TO LONDON.
I MEAN,
THAT COULD BE YOU AND EMILY.
THAT, BUT-BUT NICER.
I MEAN, JUST GO TO LONDON.
REALLY?
COME ON, SURPRISE HER.
SHOW UP AT HER DOORSTEP.
DON'T LET HER GO
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO DO IT.
I'M GOING TO...
I'M GOING TO GO TO LONDON
AND I AM GOING
TO FIGHT FOR HER.
OKAY. GOOD LUCK.
ROSS. ROSS!
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO THE AIRPORT
CAN YOU PICK ME
UP ANOTHER ONE OF
THOSE TOBLERONE BARS?
OH, OH! I DID IT.
I DID IT.
I FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO MAKE MONEY.
I'M GOING TO OPEN UP
MY OWN MASSAGE PLACE
AND FRANK'S GOING TO HELP ME
AND WE CAN WORK IT
AROUND HIS SCHEDULE
SO HE DOESN'T HAVE
TO QUIT SCHOOL.
♪ LA-LA LA-LA! ♪
THAT SOUNDS GREAT,
BUT HOW ARE YOU
GOING TO AFFORD IT?
WE WERE WALKING
DOWN THE STREET
AND SAW THAT VAN
YOU USED FOR CATERING
AND WE REALIZED THAT...
I'M TELLING IT!
OKAY.
OKAY, YOU KNOW HOW PEOPLE
NEED TRANSPORTATION
BUT THEY ALSO NEED
MASSAGES TO RELAX.
SO I JUST FIGURED
WE CAN COMBINE THE TWO.
OKAY? I GIVE THE MASSAGES
AND FRANK DRIVES.
I CAN FIX UP THE VAN
BOLT A TABLE IN BACK
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I'VE GOT?
A PLACE THAT NO ONE
WILL EVER GET OUT OF ALIVE?
WELL, NO.
THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S A TAXI THAT PEOPLE TAKE
WHEN THEY NEED TO RELAX.
IT'S A RELAXI TAXI.
THE NAME WAS MY FAVORITE PART!
WELL-WELL, I CAME UP WITH IT.
YOU DID NOT!
OH! WHAT?!
NO!
YOU CAME UP WITH "RELAXI CAB."
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
WELL...
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS, ARE YOU IN ENGLAND?
WAS EMILY SURPRISED?
NO, 'CAUSE SHE HASN'T
COME HOME YET.
SHE HASN'T BEEN HOME ALL NIGHT.
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY STAYING
WITH THAT OTHER GUY
AND I'M THE STUPID MORON
WHO SPENT THE WHOLE NIGHT
OUTSIDE HER APARTMENT.
ALL RIGHT, WHEN IS
THE NEXT FLIGHT OUT?
ABOUT FOUR HOURS.
Stay a couple more hours
and if she doesn't show up
by then, just come home.
HEY, TELL HIM
ABOUT RELAXI TAXI
AND ASK HIM IF HE THINKS
THAT'S BETTER THAN RELAXI CAB.
OKAY, IT'S NOT RELAXI CAB.
IT'S RELAXICAB-- LIKE TAXICAB.
OH, THAT IS BETTER.
( knock at door )
ARE WE IN LONDON?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU CAN'T BE HERE.
I'VE, UH...
I'VE COME TO TALK TO ROSS.
( gasps )
( moans )
WHAT?
NOTHING. NO, NOTHING.
UM, I WAS GOING
TO CALL HIM, BUT...
HA! YOU CAME TO TELL HIM
YOU LOVE HIM.
I KNEW IT!
I WAS RIGHT!
I'M RIGHT, RIGHT?
I'D REALLY RATHER TALK TO HIM.
I, UH...
I'VE BEEN TO HIS APARTMENT
AND HE'S NOT THERE AND, UH,
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM, SO...
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE HE IS?
( phone ringing )
Emily:
Ross, are you there?
YES.
I don't know
if you can hear this
but I'm going to talk anyway.
I'M IN THE STATES
WITH YOUR SISTER
AND YOUR FRIENDS
AND... IT'S ALL OVER WITH COLIN.
I came here to tell you that
and to tell you--
What?
Yes, Joey, you can have
all the chocolate you want.
Just take it.
UM...
I CAME HERE TO TELL YOU...
THAT I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO!
I'M-I'M GOING TO CALL YOU
RIGHT NOW
FROM THE PHONE BOOTH.
YOU CAN'T HEAR ME...
I WISH I COULD KNOW
IF YOU'D HEARD THAT.
I'VE EITHER TOLD YOU I LOVE YOU
OR GIVEN MY NEIGHBORS
A GOOD LAUGH.
MRS. NEWMAN,
IF YOU'RE LISTENING, BUGGER OFF.
THIS IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
I SUPPOSE THERE'S
NOT MUCH CHANCE
YOU DID HEAR THAT AND...
THERE'S THE CALL WAITING, SO...
I SHOULD GO.
OH, WELL.
HELLO?
Ross:
Hi.
ROSS, I LOVE YOU.
( sighs: )
OH...
THANK YOU.
HEY.
I WAS JUST AT THE BANK
AND THERE WAS
THIS REALLY HOT TELLER
AND SHE DIDN'T ASK ME TO GO
DO IT WITH HER IN THE VAULT.
SAME KIND OF THING
HAPPENED TO ME.
WOMAN PIZZA DELIVERY GUY
COMES OVER
GIVES ME THE PIZZA,
TAKES THE MONEY AND LEAVES.
WHAT? NO, LIKE, "NICE APARTMENT.
BET THE BEDROOMS ARE HUGE"?
NO. NOTHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE HAVE TO TURN OFF THE PORN.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. READY?
ONE...
TWO...
THREE.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
THAT'S KIND OF NICE.
YEAH, IT'S KIND OF A RELIEF.
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO SEE
IF WE STILL HAVE IT?
YEAH.
FREE PORN!
WE HAVE FREE PORN!
YEAH! YES!